[ Crowd Sounds ]
[背景音乐]
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hello, everyone.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
My name is Georgios Kontaxis,
我的名字是 Georgios Kontaxis
and together with Katie Skinner,
和我一起的是 Katie Skinner
we are both very excited to be
我们非常激动今天能来到这里
here, today, to tell you about
为大家讲述关于你的 App 和隐私
We are members of Privacy
我们是 Apple 隐私工程的
Engineering, Apple, and we work
成员
with teams across the company to
我们和整个公司的团队合作
products.
隐私
Here, at Apple, we care about
在 Apple 我们关心
And this quote from Tim Cook
以下这句话引用自 Tim Cook
reflects our philosophy.
来反映我们理念
We believe that privacy is a
我们相信隐私是一个
very basic foundation for a
优秀的 App 生态系统的
great app ecosystem.
基础
We think that great apps should
我们认为优秀的 App 应该
offer the best user experience,
提供最好的用户体验
while respecting user privacy.
并且尊重用户的隐私
So, today, you will hear some
所以  今天你将听到一些
best practices to design your
很好的方式来设计你的 App
apps with privacy in mind.
同时保护你的隐私
If you have existing apps, you
如果你有已经上架的 App
will be very interested in
你将会对我们平台
updates to our platforms which
的更新感兴趣
might affect you.
这可能会影响到你
And you will learn about some
同时你将了解到一些
exciting new privacy features
Apple 今年将要发布的
that Apple is launching, this
令人激动的
year.
我们明白  你的 App 可能依靠
on user data to deliver great
用户数据来实现
features.
优秀的功能
So, it is important that you
所以  非常重要的一点是
explain to your users how you're
你需要向你的用户解释
using their data, so they
你是如何使用他们的数据
understand what is going on and
让他们明白发生了什么
they feel comfortable engaging
让他们为使用你的 App
with your app.
感到舒适
Also, you need to get their
同时  你需要在正确的情况下
consent in the right context.
取得他们的许可
For example, as they're about to
例如  当他们准备使用一项
use a feature that relies on
需要他们数据
their data.
的功能时
iOS has built-in mediation
iOS 有针对信息透明
mechanisms for transparency and
和用户许可的
consent, and you should consider
内建调解机制
iOS also offers users control
iOS 同时提供了用户
over their privacy.
对于他们隐私的控制权
So, your apps need to handle
所以  你的 App 需要应对
cases based on the different
基于用户可能决定的不同隐私设置
privacy decisions the user might
而产生的各种情况
Here's an example of how Maps is
这里有一个例子  关于“地图”如何
using the iOS built-in
使用 iOS 内建
mechanisms to prompt for the
的机制来
user's location.
提示用户的位置
As you can see, when prompting
你可以看到  当出现提示时
Maps will clearly explain the
“地图”将清楚的解释
use cases, navigation, nearby
使用场景  导航
search results, and estimated
附近的搜索结果  以及预计
travel times.
行程时间
And if the user chooses not to
同时  如果用户选择
grant access to their location,
不授权使用位置信息
Maps is able to handle that
“地图”也能够从容地应对
gracefully and provide a subset
并提供一个它的
of its features.
功能子集
If a user allows Maps the user
如果用户允许“地图”使用位置信息
location, they will be aware
他们将会在每次使用时
each time that happens, because
被提示
there is an indicator in the iOS
因为 iOS 状态栏有一个指示器
status bar to let them know.
告知他们
And they can always go to
同时他们可以随时进入
Settings, Privacy, Location
设置  隐私  定位服务
Services, see that Maps is using
看见“地图”正在使用
their location and perhaps,
他们的位置
revise their decision.
并可以修改他们的决定
We also, know that your apps may
我们也知道你的 App 可能依赖
rely on identifiers, for
标识符
example, to personalize the user
比如  为了私人化用户经验
experience or to keep track of
或者保持对反馈信息
feedback.
的追踪
At the same time, your users
同时  你的用户
might wonder whether their
想知道他们在你的 App 上的操作
actions in your app are tied to
是会捆绑到设备
their device or to their person.
还是捆绑到
Luckily, there are great ways to
幸运的是  这里有一些很好的方法
offer privacy friendly choices,
来提供隐私友好的选择
so that users are comfortable
因此用户在使用你的 App
engaging with your apps.
时感到舒适
Specifically, identifiers can be
值得一提的是  标识符可以是随机的
random, they can be anonymous,
他们可以是匿名的
they can be short-lived, and
可以是暂时的  并且
they can be easy to reset.
他们可以被轻易重置
And iOS offers built-in API for
同时 iOS 提供了内建的 API
you to be able to generate such
让你能够生成这些
identifiers.
标识符
So, you should adopt those
所以  你应该利用这些
instead of building your own.
而不是打造自己的
As an example, consider the
例如  考虑使用
Universally Unique Identifier.
通用唯一标识符
It is a random 128-bit value,
这是一个随机的 128 位的值
which you can generate using the
你可以使用这里展示的 Swift 代码
Swift code, shown here.
来生成它
consecutive calls using this API
使用这个 API 进行三次连续的调用
unrelated values.
不相关的值
And for example, you could
作为示例  你可以
leverage the UIDs to generate
利用 UUID 来生成
short-lived identifiers.
暂时的身份标识符
For example, you can associate a
例如  你可以把你的 App
new UUID with each session in
的每次会话关联上
your app.
一个新的 UUID
Another example is the vendor
另一个例子是
identifier.
供应商标识符
It is a more stable identifier,
这是一个更稳定的标识符
because it is consistent across
因为它在与同一团队
all apps associated with the
所关联的所有 App 中
same team.
都是一致的
As you can see, here, in the
如你在这个示例表格中
example table, two apps that
看到的
belong to the same team all
两个属于同一个团队的 App
generate the same vendor
将生成同样的
identifier, while a third app
供应商标识符  而第三个
belonging to a different team
属于不同的团队
will have its own.
将有它自己的标识符
Also, keep in mind that if all
同时请记住
apps belonging to a particular
所有属于一个团队的 App
team are uninstalled from the
如果被用户卸载
user's device and later
之后重新安装
reinstalled, they will get a new
它们将会获得一个新的
identifier.
标识符
Now, let's talk about collecting
现在  让我们谈谈通过收集数据
data to enable your features.
来启用你的功能
Collecting data can be a
收集数据可以带来好处
benefit, but also, carries
但同时也携带风险
So, users might be uncomfortable
因此用户可能不愿意
giving too much of their data,
透漏太多的数据
if you do not sufficiently
如果你不能充分的说明
And also, consider the burden on
同时  请考虑管理所有数据
your end to manage all that data
并保护数据安全
and keep it safe.
的负担
So, you should consider
所以你应该考虑
aggregating data, summarizing
聚合数并整理
it, and extracting only the
数据
information you need.
你需要的信息
As an alternative, think whether
作为替代方式
a sample of the data would
请考虑是否一个数据样本就足够了
suffice, or whether you can
或者你是否可以
process the data on device
在设备上处理数据
instead of sending their all
而不将它们的值
values to your server.
发送到你的服务器
And later in this talk, you will
接下来  你将听到
hear about some great new ways
一些很好的新方式
to process data on device, using
来通过使用 iOS 硬件和软件
iOS hardware and software.
在设备上处理数据
Collecting raw data might reveal
收集原始数据可能会泄露
additional information about the
用户额外的
users.
信息
And as mentioned, this is
正如之前所提到的
information that neither your
你的用户
users nor you might want to
和你都不想
have.
这些信息存在
As an example, consider you have
比如你的 App
a new feature in your app, and
有了一项新功能
you're going to collect feedback
而你需要收集反馈信息
to see how successful it is.
来观察它是否成功
So, you could instrument your
所以  你可以使你的 App
app to send back a timestamp to
在每次用户使用新功能时
your server each time the users
发回一个
engage with your feature.
时间戳
And that would give you the
然后你的 App
information you're after.
就会给你发送你想要的信息
But if you were to plot that
但是如果你想要通过数据
data over a timeline, you could
画出一个时间线图
also learn that user one is a
你将知道用户 1
morning person, because all of
是一个在上午活跃的人
their timestamps are in the
因为他的所有时间戳
morning.
都是在早上
And user three opens your app at
而用户 3 则在晚上
night.
才使用你的 App
So, another way to collect this
另外一种
information would be to say,
收集信息的方式是
''Well, I will have my app count
让我的 App
the total number of times that a
计算一个特定的用户
particular user engages with my
使用我新功能的全部时间
feature, and send that count
然后一天一次的
back to my server, once a day.''
发送回我的服务器
And that is a more privacy
这种方式同样可以获得
friendly way to learn the same
关于新功能信息
information about the feature,
但无论是否成功
whether it's a customer or not.
它都更保护用户的隐私
But if you pay attention, you
但是如果你注意的话
might realize that now you know
你可能会意识到
that user one likes your feature
用户 1 在你所有的用户中
the most, among your users.
最喜欢你的功能
And that's not the question you
但这不是你想要
were trying to answer.
知道的事情
So, if you were to rephrase the
如果你重新阐述这个问题为
ten times a day?'' you could
你可以让你的 App
And on your end, on the server,
在你的端口 在服务器上
you could calculate the
你可以计算
percentage of users that have
超过阈值用户
exceeded the threshold.
的百分比
Keep that percentage on your
请把这个百分比记录在
server, keep track of it over
你的服务器上
time as it changes, to
来了解你的功能表现如何
specific data.
用户的特定数据
So, now let's go over some
现在让我们来了解一些更新
updates which might affect your
这可能会影响到
apps.
你的 App
I mentioned, earlier, that when
我之前提到过
apps ask for access to user data
当 App 需要使用用户数据时
iOS will prompt users for their
iOS 将会请求
consent.
用户许可
And there are cases where we
许多情况下
think that users need as much
我们认为用户需要
information as possible to make
尽可能多的信息
this decision.
来做出决定
And your app is responsible for
而你的 App 有责任
providing this additional
提供这些额外的
context.
信息
This additional context is in
这些额外的信息
the form of Purpose Strings.
使用目的字符串的形式
And Purpose Strings are included
而这些目的字符串
by iOS.
提示中
Purpose Strings are defined as
目的字符串作为 Key
keys in the Info.plist file of
定义在你的 App 下的
your app.
info.plist 文件中
And you can define those keys in
你可以在 Xcode 中定义这些 Key
Xcode, like so.
像这样
Keep in mind that those keys are
需要记住这些 Key 是
mandatory.
强制性的
So, if your app is missing a
所以  如果你的 App 缺少一个目的字符串
Purpose String and tries to
并试图访问相关数据
access related data, it will
它将终断程序
terminate with an error message
并返回一个错误信息
indicating which key is missing.
提示某个 Key 缺失
In iOS 10, these are the cases
在 iOS 10 中的这些情况下
where Purpose Strings are
目的字符串是
required.
必填的
And in iOS 11, we are making
而在 iOS 11 中
changes to Location, Photos, and
我们将对位置和图片做出改变
we're adding a Purpose String
同时我们为 CoreNFC 添加了
for Core NFC.
一个目的字符串
Core location has enabled great
CoreLocation 为你的 App
features in your apps.
开启了很好的功能
Users appreciate being able to
用户希望能够通过他们的 iOS 设备
navigate the world and find
探索这个世界
interesting places through their
并发现有趣的
iOS device.
地方
At the same time, we want users
同时  我们想要用户
to always be in control of their
总是对他们的隐私
privacy.
掌握控制权
So, in iOS 10 apps can ask for
所以在 iOS 10 中
access to the user's location at
App 可以请求在任何时候
all times, or while the app is
或者在 App 运行时
in use.
获得用户的位置信息
In iOS 11 users will be able to
在 iOS 11 中  用户将能够
choose the When In Use option at
随时选择什么时间来使用
all times.
这个选择
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
What this means for you, is that
这对你来说意味着
your app will have to account
你的 App 将不得不考虑到
for cases where the user's
当用户的位置信息
location is not available to
对你来说不可用
you.
的情况
And you need to define
而你需要
additional Purpose Strings for
额外的目的字符串
the When In Use option.
来定义何时提供选项
As a reminder, when asking for
作为提醒  当请求获得用户信息时
the user location make sure you
确保你的做法
do it in a meaningful way.
是有意义的
Make sure you prompt after the
确保你的提示
user has engaged the feature
在用户使用这个
that requires their location, so
需要位置信息的功能之后弹出
being asked for their location.
为什么他们被请求获得
When you prompt, make sure your
当你发送提示时
Purpose String provides the
确保你的目的字符串提供了
necessary information for the
必要的信息
user to make a good decision.
以供用户做出正确的选择
And if possible, try asking for
可能的话  请试着在用户
When In Use, and escalate to
体验过一段时间你的功能之后
Always after the user has some
从“使用期间”
time to experience your feature.
逐渐升级到“始终”
If you have an app on iOS 10
如果你的 iOS 10 App
that does not support the When
不支持“使用期间”
In Use option, this is the
的选项
prompt the user will see when
这就是当用户升级到 iOS 11 之后
they upgrade to iOS 11.
会看到的提示
As you can see, they can choose
如你所见  他们可以选择
the When In Use option, but
“使用期间”的选项
there is a warning that the app
但是这里有一个
does not natively support it.
App 可能不会支持的警告
If you have an app on iOS 10
如果你的 iOS 10 App
that does support both the When
同时支持“使用期间”
In Use and the Always option,
和“始终”选项
this is the prompt you will see.
这就是你会看到的提示
Both Purpose Strings will be
两个目的字符串将会
included in the prompt shown to
包括在提示中
the user.
并展示给用户
You should update your apps to
你应将你的 App 升级到
feature a single Purpose String.
支持单个目的字符串的功能
And you can do that by defining
你可以通过在你的 info.pflist 文件中
a single key in your Info.plist
定义一个单独的 Key
file, and use the Always and
来实现
So now, let's talk about Photos.
现在 让我们来谈谈照
The user's Photos library
用户的照片库
contains a lot of information.
包含了很多信息
And we want you to be able to
我们希望你能
leverage that information to
利用这些信息
deliver great features.
来提供很好的功能
At the same time, we want to
同时  我们希望
maintain a high level of user
能够高度保护
privacy.
用户的隐私
So, this year, we're adding two
所以  今年我们将为你的 App 添加
new ways for your apps to
两个新方式
interact with the Photos
来与照片库
library.
交互
Specifically, users will be able
尤其是  用户将能够
to open a photo in your app
在你的 App 中打开一张照片
without the need for you to
而不需要你请求
prompt for access to their
接入他们的
entire Photos library.
整个照片库
So, this will make them more
这样会让他们在使用你的 App 时
comfortable using your app,
感到更加舒适
because they will have better
因为他们对自己的数据
control over their data.
有了更好的控制
We're also, adding a Write only
我们同时在照片库中
access to the Photos library.
添加了一个只准写入许可
So, for example, if there's a
例如  如果这里
game that wants to save a
有一个游戏想要保存
screenshot of the user
用户成就的屏幕快照
achievements, it can prompt for
他可以提示
Write, but not Read access to
请求写入照片库而不是读取
the Photos library.
照片库
And users might be more willing
而用户可能更愿意许可
to grant that request.
这个请求
And because of these changes,
由于这些变化
when users upgrade their devices
当用户升级他们的设备到
to iOS 11, existing apps will
iOS 11 时  已安装的 App 将
re-prompt for access to the
重新请求接入
Photos library.
照片库
If you want users to be able to
如果你想要你的用户
take advantage of this ability
能够充分利用这个功能
to open Photos in your app
以在你的 App 中打开照片
adopt the Out Of Process Image
你可以采用已添加的 Image Picker 过程
Picker, and to find out more,
若要获得更多信息
This is a great way to add a
这是一个很好的方式
photo in a user's profile or use
向用户资料添加照片
a photo in some other rare
或者让你的 App 在极少数情况下
action in your app.
使用照片
Now let's look at the Write 0nly
现在  这里是一个只准写入的
case.
例子
There is a prompt and a Purpose
这里有一个提示和一个
String, so if you want to adopt
目的字符串
this, you need to decode the
你需要声明目的字符串
Purpose String.
并确保你给用户提供了
information for the users to
足够的信息
decide whether they want to use
以供他们决定是否使用
this feature.
这项功能
Now, let's talk about Core NFC.
现在  让我们来谈谈 CoreNFC
CoreNFC is a new and exciting
CoreNFC 是一个新的令人激动的
iOS 11 framework, which allows
iOS 11 框架
your app to use NFC reader modes
它允许你的 App 使用 NFC Reader 模式
to interact with nearby NFC
来和附近的 NFC Tag
tags.
进行交互
So now, you can use NFC tags in
所以  现在你可以在你的 App 中
your app in novel and
以一种新奇而有趣的方式
interesting ways.
使用 NFC tag 了
To adopt CoreNFC, you need to
为了使用 CoreNFC 你需要
declare the corresponding
声明相应的目的字符串
Purpose String and provide the
并提供必要的
necessary context.
信息
And this Purpose String will be
这个目的字符串将会包括在提示中
included in the prompt shown to
并在每次你的 App
the user every time your app
调用 CoreNFC 时
invokes CoreNFC.
提示用户
Now, let's talk about the watch.
现在  让我们来谈一谈 Apple Watch
We want your apps to be able to
我们希望你的 App 能够
do more with the watch.
更多地和 Apple Watch 互动
So, this year, we're expanding
所以  今年我们将扩展
the use of the microphone.
话筒的使用
Today, in iOS 10, your app can
现在  在 iOS 10 中
ask for microphone access, and
你的 App 能够请求话筒接入
following the user's consent, it
在得到用户许可之后
can start recording audio while
它可以开始在前台
in the foreground.
记录音频
In the new version of watchOS,
在新版的 watchOS 中
you will be able to keep
你可以在后台
And if you stay in the
如果你停留在前台
foreground you will be able to
你将可以使用
use the new API to record audio
一个新的 API 来记录音频
without showing the built-in UI.
而不展示内建 UI
Because we want users to always
因为我们想要用户总是
be aware that their microphone
意识到他们的话筒是激活的
is active, if your app is in the
如果你的 App 在后台
background, there will be an
在 Apple Watch 的表盘
indicator on the watch face.
将会有一个指示器
And if the user taps on the
而如果用户点按指示器
indicator your app will enter
你的 App 将会回到
the foreground.
前台
Let's talk about Music.
让我们来谈一谈“音乐”
We want your apps to be able to
我们希望你的 App 能够
take advantage of Music and
利用“音乐”
create great features.
并创造很棒的功能
So, part of this experience is
所以  一部分经验是
having a frictionless way to
通过一种平滑的方式
authenticate the user while
来验证用户
respecting their privacy.
同时尊重他们的隐私
So, for example, if an app were
例如  如果一个 App
to ask for the user's password
询问用户“音乐”的密码
to Music, that would be a
那将会是
privacy concern.
一个隐私问题
Instead, apps should leverage
相反 App 应该利用
the fact that the users are
用户已经在 iOS 的
already signed into Music on
Music 上登陆的
iOS.
事实
And iOS has a built-in mediation
iOS 有一个内置的调解机制
mechanism for giving your apps
来给予你的 App 令牌
access to a Music token.
来接入“音乐”
Following the user's consent,
在用户许可之后
you can get that token and use
你将会得到令牌
it to access output APIs to
并使用它访问输出 API
retrieve personalized and
来取得私人的
non-personalized information.
或者非私人的信息
For example, search the iTunes
例如  搜索 iTunes 目录
catalog or get information about
或者取得关于
the user's library.
用户资料库的信息
And remember, because the user
请记住  因为你能够控制
will have control over which
哪一个 App 能得到这个令牌
context in the Purpose String
足够的解释
for users to understand what you
你将会如何
want to do with it.
利用它
View Controller.
Safari Controller
Safari View Controller is a
Safari Controller 是一个很棒的方式
And in iOS 10 Safari cookies and
在 iOS 10 中
website data were available in
Safari 的 Cookies 以及网站数据
SVC instances, in Safari View
都可以在 SVC 实例中使用
apps.
实例的影响
This will change.
这将会改变
Now, in iOS 11 users will be
现在  在 iOS 11 中
able to use an account to log in
用户将能够在你的 App 中
a website in your app and
使用帐号登陆网站
perhaps, use a different account
而如果他们愿意的话
if they want to, to log into the
可以使用一个不同的帐号
same website in Safari, or some
在 Safari 或者其他的 App 中
other app.
登陆同样的网站
And we think that gives users
我们认为这将提供给用户
more control.
更多的控制权
Specifically, what this means is
具体而言  这意味着
that Safari and Safari View
在 Safari 中
Controller instances will have
你需要考虑使用实例
separate data stores for cookies
这将使得 Cookies 和其他的网页数据的储存
and other website's data.
分隔开来
And what this means for you and
而这对你和你的用户来说
your users, is that they will
意味着他们仍然能够
still be able to browse the web
像从前一样
in your app the same way as
在你的 App 中浏览网页
before.
但是他们可能在访问一些
again, to some of the sites they
曾经访问过的网站时
This is what it looks like.
这就是它看上去的样子
So, for example, I have
例如  我在 Safari 中
Apple.com cookies in Safari, and
有 Apple.com 的 Cookies
I have different cookies in your
而我在你的 App 中有不同的
app.
Cookies
So, this concludes the updates.
所以  以上就是更新的总结
At this point, I would like to
现在  我想
invite Katie onstage to tell you
邀请 Katie 来到台上
all about some exciting new
来告诉你一些 Apple 今年发布的
privacy features that Apple is
全新的  令人激动的
launching, this year.
隐私新功能
Katie.
Katie
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Georgios.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Georgios
Now, I'm going to focus on some
现在  我要集中介绍一些
new privacy features, as well as
新的隐私功能
provide an update on
并提供一点针对
differential privacy, that we
去年我们介绍的差别隐私
introduced last year.
的更新
I'm going to start with on
我准备从设备上处理
device processing.
开始介绍
Now, On-Device processing has a
现在  设备上处理
lot of benefits.
有很多的优点
One of the first ones, is it
其中之一就是
enables your functionality to
它能够从功能上
run anywhere your users are.
在任何你的用户所在的地方运行
Whether they're at the beach,
无论他们是在海滩
like this, or on an airplane
像这样  或者在一架飞机上
flight, or even in areas of poor
甚至在蜂窝数据信号
cellular connectivity.
不好的地方
It also, avoids network latency,
它同时避免了网络延迟
as depending on where your users
由于它取决于你的用户的位置
are, this may take longer than
这可能比你想要完成的
the actual processing that you
实际处理过程
want to accomplish.
花费更长的时间
The speed of our devices, your
我们设备的速度
iPhones, our iPads, it keeps
我们的 iPhone 和 iPad
increasing and increasing.
它的性能变得越来越强大
The iPhone 7 is 120 times the
iPhone 7 的处理能力
processing power of the original
比最初的 iPhone 提高了
iPhone.
120 倍
So, think through the different
所以  想想那些你曾经认为
tasks that you once thought were
不可能在设备上完成的
not feasible on device, and you
不同的任务
should reconsider.
你现在应该重新考虑一下了
Now, as you all are at the
现在  由于这个会议的主题是“隐私”
privacy session, I'm going to
我准备谈论一些
talk a little bit more about the
设备上处理
privacy related benefits of
在隐私方面上的
On-Device processing.
好处
One of the first ones is access
其中第一个是能够访问
to user data.
用户数据
So, there are many different
设备上有许多
types of sensitive data on
不同类型的
device.
敏感数据
And when you're clear to your
当你对用户解释清楚
users about how you plan to use
你准备怎样使用他们的数据时
that data.
举个例子
your users that the photo that
如果你告诉你的用户
with another user, or maybe back
分享给其他的用户
Then, users are going to be more
那么用户将会
likely to want to grant you
更愿意给予你
access to their data, and feel
访问他们数据的许可
more comfortable about it.
并为此感到更加的
On-Device, you can also take
舒适
advantage of all the different
利用各种不同的
security features that are built
集成在我们平台上的
into our platforms.
安全功能
These are things like data
这些功能类似数据保护
protection, the Keychain, that
就像一个钥匙串
allow you to more securely take
允许你更安全的
care of user's data, without you
使用用户数据
having to implement it,
而不需要自己去考虑它
yourself.
在过去的开发者大会上
they're a great resource for you
有很多的优秀资源
to go and learn more about these
供你去学习这些
security features.
安全功能
I would encourage you to go
我会建议你
check out ''Protecting Secrets
去查看
With the Keychain''.
“Proteting Sevrets With The Keychain（使用钥匙串保护秘密）”
It's a great place to start.
这是一个很好的入门视频
Now, when you're using and
现在  当你在设备上
keeping the data on device, that
使用并保存数据时
means you don't have to write
这意味着你不必写代码
code to send that data to your
来把数据发送到
server.
你的服务器
You don't have to write code to
你不必写代码
securely manage and make sure
来管理并确保
that, that data on your server
在你的服务器上的数据
is secure.
是安全的
Now, you all know the less code
现在你需要写的代码
you have to write, that means
变得更少
the less bugs.
这意味着更少的 Bug
And the less bugs are less bugs
而更少的 Bug 意味着
that an attacker can take
攻击者能够利用的 Bug 也
advantage of.
变少了
Because a data breach is very
因为数据破坏是
serious, and there are a lot of
非常严重的事情
consequences.
后果
But one of the consequences is
而这些后果之一是
the loss of user trust.
失去用户的信任
Now, technologies like this can
现在  这些技术同样可以
help you avoid that, as well.
帮助你避免那样的情况
Now, I'm going to talk about
接下来  我将要介绍四个
four new frameworks that allow
新的框架
you to do these common tasks on
它们允许你在设备上执行一些
device.
常见的任务
Now, any type of processing that
现在  任何在你的 App 内
you do within your app, you can
执行的处理操作
move to on device.
你都可以只在设备上完成
But here are four frameworks
但是这里有四个框架
that make it easier.
可以让它更加容易
The first one is CoreML, Core
第一个是 CoreML
Machine Learning.
Core Machine Learning（Core 机器学习）
Now, this allows you to have a
现在  它允许你使用简单的交互
simple interface to load and run
来加载并运行
pretrained models.
预训练模型
There a lot of different models
这里有许多它支持的
that it supports.
不同的模型
But one of them is neural
比如  神经网络
The second framework I'm going
第二个我准备介绍的框架
to talk about is VisionKit.
叫做 VisionKit
Now, VisionKit allows you to
现在 VisionKit 允许你在一张照片上
identify faces within a photo,
识别出面部
as well as do scene
并同样能够根据
One of the ones that I'm most
在这些框架之中
excited about is ARKit.
我最为之感到兴奋的是 ARKit
I think augmented reality is a
我认为增强现实
place where there's lots of
是一个能产生很多激动人心的东西
exciting things to come.
的领域
And I can't wait to get it in
我已经等不及将它放入
all of your hands, to see what
你们的手中
kind of experiences you guys
期待你们能为用户创造出
create for our users.
什么样的体验
Now, ARKit can allow you to
现在 ARKit 允许你
locate the device, as well as
定位设备的位置
items in the real world.
以及现实世界中物品的位置
And then, it allows you to
然后它允许你
augment on top of a camera
在相机流的顶层
stream.
进行扩充
Now, lastly, we have NLP,
最后  我们有 NLP
Natural Language Processing.
Natural Language Processing（自然语言处理）
This allows you to identify what
它允许你识别出
language a customer may have be
顾客正在输入的
entering text with, then.
可能是什么语言
tokenization, as well as named
词语切分  也叫做
entity recognition.
命名实体识别
Now, I'd encourage you to go
现在  我推荐你
check out the talk introducing
关注今天下午晚些时候会进行的
CoreML, later this afternoon.
“Introducing CoreML（介绍 CoreML）” 的会议
This will provide an overview of
它会给你提供一个
the different features available
可以在设备上利用的
that you can take advantage of
不同功能的
on device.
概览
Next, I'm going to talk about a
接下来  我准备介绍
new framework available in iOS
一个可以在 iOS 以及 Apple TVOS 上使用的
and tvOS.
新框架
It's called Device Check.
它叫做 DeviceCheck
Now, there are many developers
现在  有许多的开发者
who are currently using a
正在使用不同的技术
variety of techniques to try to
试图去
identify devices.
识别设备
Now, they may be trying to
现在  他们可能试图去
identify and answer questions
认识并回答
like, ''Has this device received
这样的问题
a free trial?
这个设备接收过免费试用吗
Has this device participated in
这个设备参与过
fraudulent activity?'' Or, ''Has
不正当活动吗
none of you in this room, may be
很多的信息
Now, to do that, they may be
没有参加过这样的活动
collecting lots of information
他们可能收集很多的信息
like, how's the device set up?
例如这个设备是怎样设置的
What information is stored on
什么样的信息
it?
存储在里面
And these developers may not
而这些开发者可能
want to have this level of
不想要这个层面的
information.
信息
All they want to do is associate
他们仅仅想要
some state with that device, in
将一些状态和特定的设备
particular.
联系起来
Now, DeviceCheck allows you to
现在 DeviceCheck 允许你将状态
associate state with the device.
和设备联系在一起
And this is done in a privacy
而且是通过一种
friendly way that you can
隐私友好的方式
achieve without collecting
你可以通过不触及非必要信息的方式
unnecessary information.
来实现它
Now, DeviceCheck allows you to
DeviceCheck 允许你
store two bits of information,
存储 2 位的信息
as well as a timestamp
同时将时间戳和设备
So, you can store 00, 01, 10, or
你可以存储 00 01 10
11.
或者 11
And it's up to you to think
这取决于你的考虑
about what this means to your
这对你的应用来说意味着什么
application and your app logic.
以及你的 App 逻辑
Now, this information will be
现在  这些信息将
maintained by Apple through
一直被 Apple 保存
until you reset it, or you
直到你重置它
update the state.
或者你更新了状态
So, this means it will be stored
所以  这意味着
by Apple through deletion of
它将被 Apple 一直保存
your app, reinstallation of your
无论你删除了
app, through erase all contents
重新安装了 App
users.
转手
Now, we know users sell devices
我们知道用户会将设备
to others.
卖给其他人
We know they transfer them to
我们知道他们会将它们转手给
other siblings or other people
他们的兄弟姐妹
they know.
或者其他认识的人
So, this information will be
这个信息在这些过程后
maintained through that.
也会保持下来
Now, as I mentioned before, it's
现在  正如我之前提到过的
up to you to figure out what
这需要你去想明白
these states mean to you.
这些状态对于你意味着什么
So, an example would be for app
例如  对于 App A
A, if a user has completed a
如果用户完成了免费试用
free trial they will be assigned
他们会被分配到一个
Now, you could have a different
现在你可以有另外一个 App
app, app B.
App B 同样的信息
been assigned or completed could
或者完成过了
be assigned 11.
可以被分配状态 11
It's up to you to make that
这需要你来做出
decision.
这个决定
Now, I want to go through the
现在  我想要演示一下整个流程
flow and make sure you guys
并确保你们明白
understand how this works in
这些在实践中
practice.
是怎样工作的
So, let's say there's an app
假如这里有一个 App
that's a news app.
那是一个新闻 App
And like I said before, it
正如我之前说到的
grants a seven day free trial.
它有一个 7 天的免费试用
So, when my free trial is
所以  当我的免费试用完成时
completed the app wants to set
App 想要将我的状态
my state to 01.
设置为 01
So, first thing it's going to do
所以  第一件发生的事情
is query for a device check
是发送请求以检查
token on device, send it to
设备上的令牌
server communication set the
设置状态
So, send over the token and the
所以  发送令牌
state that wants to be set.
以及想要设置的状态
So, then I decide that maybe I'm
然后我意识到
not a huge fan of that news app,
可能我不是非常喜欢
anymore.
这个新闻 App
I want to delete it.
我想要删除它
But then, I miss it couple of
但是几周后
weeks later, so I decide I'm
我又想念它了
going to reinstall the app.
我决定把这个 App 安装回来
On launch, that app wants to
启动时  这个 App 考虑
decide, ''should that user or
是否应该给这个用户
free trial''?
另外一次免费试用
So, query for the token, send it
所以  请询问请求令牌
to the app server the same way,
用同样的方法将它发送到 App 服务器
and this time query for the
这一次  询问这个设备
state of the device.
的状态
So, then because that device was
然后  由于这个设备
last set as 01, it will be sent
已经被设置为01
back to the app server.
它将被发送回 App 服务器
And at that point it's the app's
这个时候
job to figure out what to do,
就是 App 任务来决定接下来
next.
应该怎么做
Should that device be granted
这个设备是否应该被给予
another free trial?
另外一次免费试用
Should that device be granted,
还是设备是否应该被给予
maybe, a shorter trial?
一个短一些的试用
Or no trial at all?
或者不给予试用
It's up to you to make that
这需要你
decision.
来做出决定
So, as I said before, devices
所以  正如我之前所说
can transfer between users.
设备可以在用户之间转手
So, let's say I sell my device
假设  我将我的设备
to Georgios, because I want a
卖给了 Georgios
different phone.
因为我想要换一个手机
I want a new gold one, this
这一次我想要一个金色的
time.
Gergios 想要
install the same app.
安装同一个 App
He likes the same news app.
他喜欢同一个新闻 App
So, it's going to query for the
所以  它也将用同样的方式
token the same way, send it to
询问令牌并将它
its app server, and then, query
发送回 App 服务器
Again, 01 will be returned.
同样的 01 将会被返回
And this case, Georgios has not
而这种情况下
gotten a free trial.
Georgios 还没有购买免费试用
So, you need to think about how
所以  你需要考虑
to handle these type of cases.
如何解决这些情况
Now, make sure that you have a
现在  你要确保
way that customers can reach out
用户有和你联系的方式
experiencing issues with this.
可以进行升级
And they need to come and reach
他们需要来联系你
out to you, because at Apple, we
因为 Apple
don't have any idea what these
并不知道这些状态
states correspond to.
对应的是什么
So now, I'm going to quickly go
现在  我将要快速的展示一下
through what a sample query
一个询问的例子
could look like.
看起来是什么样的
As you can see, here's the
如你所见
device token, the transaction
这是一个设备令牌
ID, which you generate, as well
你生成的交易 ID
as a timestamp.
以及一个时间戳
Then, here's the response from
然后  这里是 Apple
Apple with the state.
反馈的状态
And then, if you want to update
然后  如果你想要升级状态
the state, again have the device
同样
token, your transaction ID that
请获取设备令牌
you generate, as well as the
生成的交易 ID
timestamp and the state you want
以及时间戳
When you're using DeviceCheck
当你使用 DeviceCheck 时
make sure to think through these
确保考虑到这些
best practices.
实际情况
Make sure you handle the case
确保你能解决
where devices are transferred
设备在用户之间转手
between users.
的情况
A device's behavior can change
一个设备的行为
over time.
可能随着时间变化
Additionally, think about the
此外
recency of the data.
请考虑数据的更新
If the state was set a year,
如果这个数据是一年前设置的
different to you than if it was
可能会有
this month.
不同的意义
This should be part of your
它们应该组成你的 App 逻辑的一部分
app's logic, but not the sole
而不仅仅是资源
And think through how you
此外  请考虑如何将这个状态
When Georgios goes to launch the
当 Georgios 第一次启动这个 App 时
app for the first time, you want
你会想要给他
to have a fresh experience for
留下一些崭新的
him.
印象
So, make sure you think through
所以  确保你考虑到
that.
这些
Now, you should be using
你应该使用
platform supported identifiers.
平台支持的身份标识符
These are the application
这些是应用标识符
identifier, the vendor
供应商标识符
identifier, as well as the
以及
advertising identifier.
广告标识符
We will continue to remove and
我们会继续将
to remove entropy on our
冗余从 App 沙箱中清除
And as we have before, we will
正如我们之前做的
continue to identify areas of
我们会继续锁定冗余区域
entropy and put them either
并将他们交给
behind user control or remove
用户控制或者
them.
直接移除
Next, I'm going to talk about
接下来  我打算谈一谈
Intelligent Tracking Protection.
智能追踪保护
This year, we're working to
今年  我们致力于
reduce cross-web tracking.
减少跨网络追踪
Now, since the beginning, WebKit
现在 WebKit
and Safari have been leaders in
以及 Safari 已经成为
user privacy.
用户隐私保护的领导者
One example of this is blocking
其中的一个例子是
third party cookies by default.
默认拦截第三方的 Cookies
Now, I want to get this out
现在  我想提出这个
there, that Intelligent Tracking
智能追踪保护
Protection is not about blocking
不在于拦截
content.
内容
That's not what this technology
那不是这个技术的
is.
关键
It dynamically detects online
它会自动的检测到
tracking across the sites that a
通过用户访问网站的
user visits.
追踪
And using an on-device
然后通过使用一个
classifier, it will identify
设备上的分类器
tracking domains.
它将识别追踪域
Once a tracking domain is
一旦追踪域被识别
identified, then it will isolate
它将会隔绝
the third party cookies, as well
第三方 Cookies
as website data for that
以及那个网站的
website.
网站数据
And then, periodically, that
然后数据将会周期性的
data will be purged.
被清洗
that domain, that is taken as a
和那个网域有交互
signal that the user is
这将会被当作一个信号
interested in that website.
说明用户对那个网站感兴趣
whitelisted.
白名单
So, let's go through an example.
让我们回顾一个例子
So, if example.com is identified
如果 example.com 被识别为
as a tracker, and the user
一个追踪网站
visits site 1, that embeds
用户访问了网站 1
example.com, example.com will
网站 1 嵌入了 example.com
set the cookie foo.
example.com 将 Cookies 设置为 foo
Now, a user goes to site 2,
现在用户访问了网站 2
which also embeds example.com,
网站 2 同样嵌入了 example.com
but here, example.com does not
但是这里 example.com 将
have access to the cookie foo.
没有权限设置 Cookies 为 foo
So, then it will set cookie bar.
所以它将设置 Cookies 为 bar
And then, over time these
过段时间之后
cookies will be purged.
这些 Cookies 将被清洗
Now, no cookies will be deleted
现在  第一个网站的 Cookies
from first party websites.
将不会被删除掉
Additionally, if the user
此外  如果用户
interacts with your website via
和你的网站有交互
click, a tap, entering a form,
通过点击  点按的方式
then note it will be
它将立刻进入白名单
You should not rely on storage
如果你的用户
if the user does not interact
不与你的网站进行交互
with your website.
你就不应该依赖存储的方式
And this is an important one to
理解这一点
understand; if your analytics
非常重要
So, what we're trying to
所以  我们这里试图实现的是
achieve, here, is that users
用户只有与他们
that they actually intersect
和 Cookies
with.
真正产生交互的网站
And then, all the other tracking
然后所有用户浏览的
as the user navigates and visits
其他追踪网站
websites will be proactively
将会主动的
removed.
被移除
Lastly, we have an update on
最后  我们对于差别隐私
Differential Privacy.
有一个更新
So, Differential Privacy was
差别隐私于去年
launched on iOS and macOS, last
在 iOS 和 macOS 上
year.
发布
Since then, we've collected
从那以后 我们每天可以收集
millions of privately donated
数百万捐赠的
data per day, and it allowed us
私人数据
to build user features with
来建造用户隐私
privacy.
功能
Now, I want to talk about two
现在  我想介绍两种
new use cases, this year.
今年的新用途
The first one is collecting what
第一个用途是是收集
data is commonly stored in
通常储存在 HealthKit 中的是什么
HealthKit.
数据
Now, one of the challenges of
其中一个研究敏感功能
or features that have sensitive
的挑战
data, is you want to understand
是你想要理解这些功能
how those features are being
是怎样
used.
被使用的
You want to understand what's
你想要理解当用户
resonating, where users are
产生失误操作
falling into issues or errors
或者发生错误时
are occurring.
的感受
But you know that collecting
但是你知道
data about what they're actually
收集关于他们真正交互的信息
interacting with may have more
可能会包含
information than you really
比你所需要的更多的
need.
信息
So, one example here is, if you
这里有一个例子
collect what type of data, what
如果你收集什么类型的数据
data types the user has stored
什么类型的数据存储在他们的设备上
on their device, things like
例如
blood glucose.
血糖
Things like Workout, that could
例如锻炼这些
information about their health
可能包含更多的
And we don't really need that
而我们并不真正需要
level of information.
那个层面的信息
So, that's why it's so exciting
所以  这就是为什么
to have Differential Privacy at
Apple 拥有差别隐私是令人激动的
Apple, because we can still get
因为我们仍然可以
information to continue to
得到足够的信息
iterate and build our features,
来不断构造我们的功能
while respecting user privacy.
但同时尊重用户的隐私
So, last year in the Privacy
所以  在去年隐私会议
session at the Developer
和开发者大会上
Conference, Julian [assumed
Julian 在深入探究
deep-diving into how
差别隐私在 Apple
Differential Privacy works at
是如何工作上
Apple.
完成的很好
Basically, we collect privatized
基本上  我们收集了私有的捐赠
donations like emoji, and as
例如表情符号
more and more users contribute
随着更多的用户贡献
these privatized emojis, we
他们的私人表情符号
learn what are the most popular
我们知道了什么是
But the key part here, is we
但是  关键点在于
learned nothing that's
我们并不知道
associated by an individual
和个体用户相关的
user.
信息
For more information about how
关于更多 Apple 的差别隐私
Differential Privacy works at
是如何工作的信息
Apple, I would encourage you all
我建议你们
to look at our session from last
去了解去年在开发者大会中
year's Developer's Conference.
的会议
So, this year we're applying the
今年我们打算将
same process to health data
同样的过程放到
types.
健康数据类型上
So, we will learn the most
所以  我们将会了解
popular health data types, but
最流行的健康数据类型
with learning nothing about the
而不获得个体用户的
individual user.
信息
The second case is trying to
第二个情况是
learn websites that either are
去了解那些非常缓慢
very slow or take up a lot of
或者占用了太多电池寿命的
battery life.
网站
We all want a fast, speedy web.
我们都想有一个快速的网站
But we don't necessarily want to
但是我们不必要知道
learn everything that a user is
用户浏览的一切
visiting.
信息
That's a lot of information
那是很多关于用户的信息
about that user, depending on
取决于他们的
their web searches.
网络搜索
So, this is another example
这是另外一个例子
where we get to use Differential
我们使用了差别隐私
Privacy to then, reach out to
然后接触了那些
these developers who maybe, have
可能拥有这些问题
issues or are writing slow
或者写了慢速网站的开发者
So, then we can improve the web
因此我们能够为每一个人
for everyone.
改善那些网站
Now, in summary, we are all here
现在  总结一下
today, and listening online and
我们今天在这里
here this week in an effort to
或在在网络上参加会议
build great features for our
是为了给我们的用户提供
users.
优秀的功能
Make something that our users
创造一些我们的用户会喜欢的
will love.
东西
think is fun, or maybe makes
认为有趣的东西
their lives easier, their jobs
或者让他们生活的更便捷
easier.
让他们的工作更轻松
And what I want you to take away
我想让你
from the past 40 minutes, is
在过去 40 分钟得到的
several techniques and concepts
是一些可以使用到你的 App 中的
that you can apply within your
几项技术和
own app.
概念
The first one is consent and
第一个是用户许可和
transparency.
信息透明
Make sure to think about what
确保考虑到
you're saying in your Purpose
你想表达什么
Strings and be clear to your
以及你的目的字符串
Also, adopt While In Use
这同样适用于
location.
需要使用定位信息时
Together, we can build a healthy
我们可以一起建造出一个
app ecosystem, and DeviceCheck
健康的 App 生态系统
is part of that.
而 DeviceCheck 就是其中的一部分
We want to build a healthy web
我们想要为每一个人
for everyone, and Intelligent
建造出一个健康的网站环境
With Differential Privacy, we're
一部分
building features and learning
我们将会开发新功能
how to build better features,
并学习如何开发更好的功能
while protecting user privacy.
同时保护用户的隐私
Now, one of the great things
现在 我在 Apple 工作的
about my job at Apple is I get
最美好的部分之一
to work with a bunch of
是能够和许多
different teams.
不同的团队工作
to build fantastic features and
很棒的功能和 API 而努力工作
APIs for you guys to take
以使你们能够利用起来
And that same passion, I get to
和这些优秀的人
apply and work with great people
一起工作的激情
to apply to building privacy in,
也是我一开始决定
from the start.
实现隐私保护的激情
And making sure that we all are
确保我们都在
building great features and
创造优秀的功能
respecting users' privacy.
并且尊重了用户的隐私
And what I want you to take away
然后  我想让你们
from this is a bit of
从这里得到的
inspiration.
是一点启发
Go home, work with the teams
回家吧  和你的团队一起工作
that you have, and go build
去创造让人为之惊讶
great features that will
为之喜悦的优秀功能
Now, for more information,
要想了解更多的信息
please go to this link.
请访问这个链接
And we mentioned a lot of topics
我们在这次谈话中提到了
during this talk.
很多的话题
And so, I'd encourage you to go
因此  我建议你们
check out some of these related
去查看一些相关的会议
sessions, including the CoreML
包括今天下午晚些时候
one that's later this afternoon.
举办的与 CoreML 相关的会议
Thank you, very much.
非常感谢各位到来
And have a great Developer
祝大家度过一个愉快的开发者大会
[ Applause ]
[掌声]